4/4/23, 5:17 PM My Resume

Mohamed Saleh Mahfouz Frontend Developer

https://github.com/Saleh0987 in https://github.com/Saleh0987 in https://www.linkedin.com/in/saleh23/

Summary

Hello there I'm a Frontend Web Developer who has 1+ years of team work experience and open source contributions, I enjoy building everything with JavaScript. In this duration, I have learned a lot of technologies, created many cool websites, collaborated with great developers and contributed to open source projects.

Education

> Bachelor's Degree in Department of Management Information Systems

The Higher Institute for Advanced Studies, Cairo 2016 - 2021

Experience

>JavaScript Frontend Developer - Internship

Intern2Grow - Remote April 2023 - Present

>Frontend Developer

Google Developer Groups Assiut - Tech Team January 2023 - Present

Projects

> Ecommerce Shop

A website to buy and sell products and browse them.

- Built with { HTML5, CSS3, React.js, Redux-Toolkit, Firebase }
- View at >Here

> Movix api App

Knowing the latest series and movies on international platforms and knowing everything about them.

- Built with { HTML5, Scss, React.js, Redux, API }
- View at >Here

127.0.0.1:5501/index.html

4/4/23, 5:17 PM My Resume

> Modern Nike Store

An e-commerce site for selling NIKE shoes, you can add them to the shopping cart and complete browsing through it.

- Built with { HTML5, TailwindCss, React.js, Redux-Toolkit, Vite }
- View at ≯Here

> Code-Editor - With-Team

A website where you can practice coding in html, css and js, and save your projects.

- Built with { HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6 }
- View at >Here

Certificates

- > Coursera certified Frontend Web Developer
- Verify at >Here
- > Coursera certified HTML and CSS in depth
- Verify at >Here
- > freeCodeCamp certified JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Verify at >Here
- > CodeLearn certified JavaScript Basics
- Verify at >Here

Skills

> HTML5

JavaScript (ES6)jQuery

> SASS

> Redux & Redux toolkit

> TailwindCss

> CSS3

> JSON

> Bootstrap

> React.js

> Next.js

Languages

- > Arabic native
- > English good

Community Activities

> Head OC

Google Developer Groups Assiut, Present

127.0.0.1:5501/index.html 2/2